football370.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy - Football370

We at Planet Sport Publishing, (incorporating this site and all of the sites within our network – as seen on the footer of this website), strongly believe in protecting the confidentiality and security of information we collect about individuals. The material below describes our privacy policy and describes how we treat the information we receive about you if you interact with any of our sites.  
Why We Need to Know About You  
We need to know about you so that we can provide you with information on products and services and better target our sports content offering to your interests. What we need to know about you includes your address, age and preferences.

How We Learn About You  
What we know about you we get mostly from you. But we may also have to find out more about you from other sources in order to make sure that what we know about you is correct and complete. We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from competitions, message boards, suggestions and transactional areas.

Your Right To Opt Out  
At our points of data collection, you have the opportunity to indicate whether you would like to “opt in” or “opt out” of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from group companies and/or third parties on whose behalf we may send out information. Further, notwithstanding any opt out of promotional information by the user, we reserve the right to contact you regarding account status, changes to our service agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. You can request to “opt out” of further promotional contacts at any time and all promotional emails we send you allow you this facility. Also, upon request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts functionally to delete you and your personal information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete your entry without some residual information due to backups and records of deletions.

How We Protect What We Know About You  
We treat what we know about you confidentially. Our employees take care in handling your information. They may get information about you only when there is a good reason to do so. We take steps to make our databases secure and to safeguard the information we have about you.

How We Use and Disclose What We Know About You  
We may use anything we know about you to help us serve you better. We will not disclose your information to any third party save for the following exceptions:

To help us process questions you may have about a purchase, registration or other inquiry you may have.  
To confirm or correct what we know about you.  
To help us or law enforcement agencies prevent fraud, money laundering, terrorism and other crimes.  
To allow for verification of what we know about you.  
Data processing requirements.  
Assisting an agency perform research for us.  
Compliance with the law or request of a government agency for example, complying with a search warrant.  
Compliance with an audit our business.  
If we sell all or any part of our business or merge with another company.  
Generally, we will disclose only the information we consider reasonably necessary to disclose.

How You Can See and Correct Your Information  
Generally, we will let you review what we know about you if you ask us in writing or email. If you tell us that what we know about you is incorrect, we will review it. If we agree with you, we will correct our records.

Third Party Data Collection  
You should be aware that sites within the group might sometimes permit third parties to offer you subscription, registration-based services, promotions or competitions through our network. We are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information to other parties.

Sharing Your Data in Public Areas of our Sites  
You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) on any of our message boards, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control.

How We Use IP Addresses  
We may use your IP address to help diagnose any problems with our server or to administer our websites. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information that helps us understand user requirements. This specific information will only be used within our organisation and we will only share or use this information on an aggregate basis.

Links to Other Sites  
Our site contains links to other sites outside of our control. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices or the content of such websites.
